const DSA = [
    {
        question: "How can we describe an array in the best possible way?",
        options:[ "The Array shows a hierarchical structure.", "Arrays are immutable.", "Container that stores the elements of similar types", "The Array is not a data structure"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the process of inserting an element in the stack?",
        options:[ "Insert", "Add", "Push", "None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "The time complexity of enqueue operation in Queue is __",
        options:[ "O(1)", "O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(n * log n)"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is not the application of the Queue data structure?",
        options:[ "Resource shared between various systems", "Data is transferred asynchronously", "Load balancing", "Balancing of symbols"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following statement is not true regarding the priority queue?",
        options:[ "Processes with different priority can be easily handled", "Easy to implement", "Deletion is easier", "None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What would be the time complexity if user tries to insert the element at the end of the linked list (head pointer is known)?",
        options:[ "O(1)", "O(n)", "O(log n)", "O(n * log n)"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following techniques is not used in the Binary tree?",
        options:[ "Randomized traversal", "Preorder traversal", "Postorder traversal", "Inorder traversal"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following data structure allows you to insert the elements from both the ends while deletion from only one end?",
        options:[ "Input-restricted queue", "Output-restricted queue", "Priority queue", "None of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is not the type of the Queue?",
        options:[ "Linear Queue", "Circular Queue", "Double ended Queue", "Single ended Queue"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the advantage of the array data structure?",
        options:[ "Elements of mixed data types can be stored.", "Easier to access the elements in an array", "Index of the first element starts from 1.", "Elements of an array cannot be sorted"],
        answer: 2
    }
];

export default DSA;